All this time we’ve been together
And I still don’t know how you feel
Sometimes I wish you’d just
Talk to me
Maybe it’s make believe
Maybe it can be true
I try to tell myself
I’m not in love with you
I thought that I knew everything
I guess I don’t know anything, yeah
I get emotional
And hypothetical
Wondering if there are all kinds of things
I’m not supposed to know
I try my best to let it go
Baby then you bring me back
Bring me back
You lift my feet off of the ground
Keep me spinning around and around
I don’t ever wanna come down
From your arms
You tell me that you need me
Then you walk away
Keep promising forever
With the words you say
It’s true
Don’t know what I’m supposed to do
I’m stuck in the middle with you you you
With you you
Oh boy you got me really confused
Don’t know what I’m supposed to do
I’m stuck in the middle with you
You were the spark
Light in the dark
Gave you my everything
Pulling me in
Pushing me out
Pulling me back again
Don’t know if your mind is made up
But I know that nobody wanna be stuck
You are the one that I want
All I can promise you now is my love
You say you want me
You say you care
When we’re together
Are you even there
And you
Gave me the keys (to your heart)
Yeah you
Made me believe (from the start)
Now all that I know is
I got all this love I won’t take back
My love
You lift my feet off of the ground
Keep me spinning around and around
I don’t ever wanna come down
From your arms
You tell me that you need me
Then you walk away
Keep promising forever
With the words you say
It’s true
Don’t know what I’m supposed to do
I’m stuck in the middle with you you you
With you you
Oh boy you got me really confused
Don’t know what I’m supposed to do
I’m stuck in the middle with you
I’ve tried and I’ve tried to be good to myself
Good for my health
Is it selfish
If I’m constantly turning to you
To you
If you knew what I’m feeling right now
You’d comfort my heart
You tell me that you need me
Then you walk away
Keep promising forever
With the words you say
It’s true
Don’t know what I’m supposed to do
I’m stuck in the middle with you you you
With you you
Oh boy you got me really confused
Don’t know what I’m supposed to do
I’m stuck in the middle with you